<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Formlabs :: CID guide website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/index.html</link>
    <description>The FormLabs resin printer is the highest detail printer here in the CID and can create incredibly fine figures. Printing upside-down on the print bed, the FormLabs printer is one of the slower but more precise printers. To use it follow these guides:&#xA;Uploading Files&#xA;Print Settings&#xA;Printing&#xA;Removing From Bed&#xA;Washing and Baking&#xA;Changing Resin</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:34:44 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Uploading Files</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/uploadingfiles/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:34:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/uploadingfiles/index.html</guid>
      <description>To upload files to the FormLabs printer first open the PreForm application.&#xA;Then drag and drop your intended file into the work area of the window&#xA;From here you have a few options about how to set up your print.&#xA;One Click Print The simplest is to hit the ( ) icon and use One Click Print&#xA;Hit the Set Up Your Print button and the app will automatically rotate your model and add supports for the best print generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printer Settings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/printersettings/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:33:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/printersettings/index.html</guid>
      <description>Now that you have your print set up, click the Printer button in the top left.&#xA;Choose Printer Under the choose printer section, select the dropdown and select Form 3/3+.&#xA;Then underneath should appear a row named AzureGoshawk which you should select.&#xA;Choose Material Select whatever material is currently loaded in the printer.&#xA;Choose Layer Thickness Layer thickness will change how fast the file prints as well as the resolution of the product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/printing/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:33:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/printing/index.html</guid>
      <description>Once you are ready to print, hit the Upload Print button and a menu will appear. This is the same menu that will appear when you use the One-Click Print feature.&#xA;In this menu you can either press Add to Queue or Print Now.&#xA;Add to Queue adds it to the list of prints available on the printer.&#xA;Print Now starts the job immediately. Your object should print shortly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing Print</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/removingfrombed/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:32:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/removingfrombed/index.html</guid>
      <description>To remove the print from the bed, first put on latex gloves as resin can be harmful to your skin with frequent contact.&#xA;Then open the casing around the printer by pulling up on the handle.&#xA;Inside, you will see your print attached upside-down to the print bed, and a mechanism holding the bed.&#xA;Unhook the latch holding the bed on and remove the print bed.&#xA;From there, get a scraper and carefully use it to pry the print off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washing and Baking</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/washingandbaking/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:32:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/washingandbaking/index.html</guid>
      <description>These steps will use the two black machines next to the Formlabs printer.&#xA;with labels.&#xA;First, take your pieces and place them in the washing basin.&#xA;Click the knob to power the machine on, and then click it again to start the washing. You can change the settings with the dial but they will be set up for washing for you.&#xA;.&#xA;Once your pieces are done washing, you can take them out and move them into the second black box, to bake them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing Resin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/changingfilament/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:32:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/3dprinters/formlabs/changingfilament/index.html</guid>
      <description>Please do not attempt to change resin yourself. Get help from a trained adult if you need a different resin type.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>